

+61 458 398 221

shilpakur18@gmail.com LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Reliable and focused person with 2 years of experience in C#, .Net Framework, Microsoft Azure, Azure Logic apps, Angular and SQL. Expertise in Client support by checking for bugs and weakness by efficient troubleshooting methods and providing enhancements to code bases as part of the upgrade.

SKILLS

. Net Framework

C#

Angular

SQL

Microsoft Azure

Azure Logic Apps

Data Factory

Trouble Shooting

Stored Procedures

Web API

SHILPA KURIAKOSE

EXPERIENCES

<u>Senior Software Engineer – LTI Mindtree | Chennai, India</u>

MARCH 2021 - JAN 2024

- Skilled in .Net Framework, C#, Angular, RPA, Azure Services and SQL. Experienced in working with Azure Integration Services such as Logic Apps, Azure Functions, Data Factory and Azure Storage.
- Checked client codes for bugs and weakness according to the approved troubleshooting methods and provided quick fixes.
- Updated code bases for the enhancements proposed by the clients.
 Net Framework Update, Azure Function Version Update.
- Responsible for direct client interactions as primary point of contact for associated applications.
- Made changes to the stored procedures as per client requirements.
- Deployed solutions using CICD Azure pipelines, modifying YAML files to suit cloud application configurations.
- Consistently delivered on time and with positive feedback, including 5+ client proposals on short notice by utilizing effective task prioritization, testing, and change management skills.
- Developed backend web API from scratch using .NET Framework for client applications.
- Developed Azure Logic apps for the project which integrates blob storage, COSMOS DB and service bus.
- Automated several refinery scheduling procedures using Azure Data Factory.

<u>Software Engineer – LTI Mindtree | Chennai, India</u>

FEB 2021- AUGUST 2021

- Skilled in .Net Framework, C#, Angular, RPA, Azure Services and SQL. Experienced in working with Azure Integration Services such as Logic Apps, Azure Functions, Data Factory and Azure Storage, RPA
- Checked client codes for bugs and weakness according to the approved troubleshooting methods and provided quick fixes.
- Supported an RPA application that performs automation. Had been an integral part in enhancements to the code bases as per client requirements.
- Updated code bases for the enhancements proposed by the clients.

Graduate Engineer Trainee – LTI Mindtree | Chennai, India

OCT 2020 - FEB 2021

- Trained in C#, Angular and SQL
- Developed an application called Online Examination System with C# as front end, Angular as Backend and SQL as data storage.

PROJECTS

EMED DOMGAS, BLEND REPORTS

MARCH 2021 - PRESENT

- Emed Domgas is an application built in .NET Core with Angular back end that is used to allocate gas to the customers from refineries.
- Blend Reports An Oil and Gas Manufacturing Application built in .Net Core that is used to reconcile blends for recipes.
- Key Resources SQL, Azure Logic Apps, Blob Storage Key Responsibility – Application Support and Development.
- Had been an integral part in troubleshooting issues from back end (Web Api) and logic app functionalities.
- Performed activities related to Disaster Recovery Plan.
- Good hands-on experience on stored procedures during data issue fix.

EDUCATION

JUNE 2020

Bachelor of Engineering | Computer Science Engineering Madras Institute of Technology, Chennai, India

REFERENCES

Mr. Manoj Bharthi Senior Specialist – LTIMindtree

Manojramesh.bharti@ltimindtree.com Ph: +91 720 853 2542

Mr. Rakesh Kumar gupta

Specialist – Cloud Engineering – LTIMindtree

Rakeshkumar.gupta@ltimindtree.com Ph: +91 906 306 6308

Mrs. Akshita M Senior Consultant – LTIMindtree

Akshita.mehta@ltimindtree.com Ph: +91 976 833 2638

.....